A Finding Aid to the Frank K. M. Rehn Galleries Records, 1858-1969 (bulk 1919-1968), in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Correspondence, A-Z, 1858-1969; undated; Series 1; Archival Resource Key; (Boxes 1-15; 14.4 linear feet; Reels 5849-5869)
  - Berlandina - Billingsley, B. H., circa 1922-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Reel 5851, Frame 1522-1579)
    Best, David
    Frank Best and Co.
    Beverly Hills Hotel and Bungalows
    Bianco, Pamela
    Biddle, E. T.
    Biddle, George
    Bier, Justus
    Biggs, Mr. and Mrs. Walter, II
    Billingsley, B. H.
  - Biltmore Art Salon - Bingham Photo Engraving Co., Inc., circa 1922-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Reel 5852, Frame 13-26)
    Biltmore Art Salon (See also Cowie Galleries)
    Binford, Julien
    Bing and Bing
    Bingham, Mrs. A. W.
    Bingham Photo Engraving Co., Inc.
  - Birch - Bixby, 1924-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Reel 5852, Frame 27-86)
    Birch, Beatrice W.
    Birmingham Museum of Art
    Birren, Joseph
    Bissell, Mrs. Alfred E.
    Bixby, Barbara
  - Blackburn - Harrison Blum Gallery, 1920-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Reel 5852, Frame 87-168)
    Blackburn, William
    Blagden, Alison
    Blagden, F. Allen
    Blagden, Thomas P.
    Blaikie, Robert B.
    Blair, Lee
    Blair, Robert N.
    Blanch, Arnold
    Blanchard, Mrs. John Osgood
    Blanchard, Mrs. W. S.
    Blemmer, Carl J.
    Blevins, Jacques E.
    Bliss, Robert Woods and Mildred
    Bliss, Mrs. William H.
    Block, Leigh B.
    Block, Ralph
    Bloedel, Eleanor
    Blomshield, John
    Bloomberg, Marguerite
    Bloomington Art Association
    Blow, Mrs. Richard
    Blue Cross, Blue Shield
    Blum, E. C.
    Harrison Blum Gallery
  - Bock - Boyer, 1919-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Reel 5852, Frame 170-257)
    Bock, Eugene
    Boehret, Ethel W.
    Bofinger Bros.
    Bohrod, Aaron
    Bolles, Charles S.
    Bolles, Reginald F.
    Bontous, August
    Book-of-the-Month Club, Inc.
    Boone, C. L.
    Borden, Ella
    Borgatta, Isabel Case
    Bosa, Louis
    Boshkoff, Douglass G.
    Bossert, John
    Boston Art Club
    Boston Arts Festival
    Boston Public Library
    Boston Safe Deposit and Trust Company
    Boston Symphony Orchestra
    Boston Truck Co., Inc.
    Boswell-Frankel Advertising Service
    Boswell, Helen
    Boswell, Peyton
    Botkin, Henry
    Bourgeois Gallery
    Boutwell, Cyrus
    Bowdoin College
    Bower, Alexander
    Bower, Anthony
    Bowker, Nancy
    Boyd, Fiske
    Boyd's City Dispatch
    Boyer, C. P.
  - Brackett - Braus Art Galleries, 1918-1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Reel 5852, Frame 258-329)
    Brackett, Clare L.
    Brackman, Robert
    Bradley, Susan H. (Mrs. L.)
    Bradley, Mrs. M. P.
    Bradley, Vinnie
    Brady, Mrs. James Cox
    Brainard, Owen
    Brainos, M.
    Bram, Mrs. William
    Braman, Chester A. and Gladys
    Brandeis University, Rose Art Museum
    Brandt, Lois
    Brandt, Rex
    Braught, Ross E.
    Braun, Herman L.
    Braun, John F. and Edith E.
    Braus Art Galleries
  - Brearley and Bradley - Bremer, 1919-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Reel 5852, Frame 330-462)
    Brearley and Bradley
    William S. Brecker and Co./Brecker, Zucker and Co.
    Breckinridge, Robert
    Breckner, George, Jr.
    Bredin, R. Sloan
    Breithut, Florence
    Breithut, Frederick E.
    Bremer, S. J.
  - Bresnahan - A. Bronstein Company, 1924-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Reel 5852, Frame 463-516)
    F. H. Bresler Co./Bresler Galleries
    Bresnahan
    Brett, Wyckoff, Potter Hamilton, Inc.
    Breyer, Margaret
    Bridgeport Hydraulic Co.
    Briggs, L. Vernon
    Briggs, Norma
    Brigham, Katherine L.
    Bristol Art Museum
    British War Relief Society, Inc.
    Brittain, Miller
    Brixey, R. D.
    Brodman, Keeve
    Broemel, Carl
    Bronson, Barbara
    A. Bronstein Company
  - Brook, Alexander, 1944-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Reel 5852, Frame 517-992)
  - Miss Brooke Interiors, 1926; undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Reel 5852, Frame 993-994)
  - Brooklyn Museum, 1921-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Reel 5852, Frame 995-1114)
  - Brooks - Bryn Mawr Art Center, 1921-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Reel 5852, Frame 1115-1196)
    Brooks, Jim
    Brooks, Karolyn B.
    Brooks, Mae M.
    Brooks Memorial Art Gallery
    Brooks, Van Wyck
    Brooks, W. F.
    Brown, Agnes Clare
    Brown, Alexander
    Brown, Burr R.
    Brown, Carroll
    Brown, Catrinka
    Brown, Mrs. Dudley
    Brown, Mrs. E. P.
    Brown, George Elmer
    Brown, Gladys A.
    Brown, Gwyneth (See King, Gwyneth Brown)
    Brown, Harold William
    Brown, Henry Collins
    Brown, Irving
    Brown, J. G.
    Brown, Mr. and Mrs. John Welburn
    Brown, Joseph
    Margaret Brown Gallery
    Brown, T. Wistar
    Brown Transfer and Storage Service
    Brown Wheelock-Harris Voght Co.
    Brownlee, Gale
    Bruce, Margaret S.
    Bruggey, Delwin
    Brush, Jerome
    Bruten, Milton
    Bruyn, Eveline
    Bryant Park Sculpture Guild
    Bryn Mawr Art Center
  - Buchanan - Bucknell University, 1921-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Reel 5852, Frame 1197-1261)
    Buchanan, Charles
    Buchsbaum, Myron
    Buck, George H.
    Buck Hill Art Association
    Buckingham, Kate S.
    Buckley, Alice
    Buckley, Charles E.
    Bucknell University
  - W. S. Budworth and Son, Inc. - Bunker, 1921-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Reel 5852, Frame 1262-1341)
    W. S. Budworth and Son, Inc.
    Buena Vista College
    Buffalo and Erie Country Historical Society
    Buford, Leonise
    Bugbird, Mary Bayne
    Bullard
    Bullock's Grocery
    Bunker, Arthur H.
  - Burchfield, Charles E. and Bertha, 1929-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Reel 5852, Frame 1342-1578)
  - Burchfield, Charles E. and Bertha, cont., 1929-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Reel 5853, Frame 13-389)
  - Burchfield Estate - Butcher, 1923-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Reel 5853, Frame 390-505)
    Burchfield Estate
    Burchfield Foundation
    Burchfield, L.
    Burchfield, Martha Richter
    Burchfield-Penney Art Center (See State University College at Buffalo)
    Burden-Muller, Rowland
    Burden, William A. M.
    Burgoon, E. B.
    Burket, Carol
    Burns, Howard F.
    Burrelles Press Clipping Bureau
    Burrer, Robert M.
    Burrill, Nell F.
    Burroughs, Alan
    Burroughs, Betty (See also Woodhouse, Betty Burroughs)
    Burrows, Carlyle
    Burrows, Gladys
    Burt, R. M.
    Burton, Irving F.
    Burton, Margaret L.
    Bush, H. C.
    Bush, Mary L.
    Bustany, A. B.
    Butcher, Larry
  - Butler Art Institute/Butler Institute of American Art/Butler, Joseph G., 1940-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Reel 5853, Frame 506-607)
  - D. B. Butler and Co. - California Watercolor Society, 1918-1951; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Reel 5853, Frame 608-667)
    D. B. Butler and Co.
    Butler, Joseph G. (See Butler Art Institute)
    Butler, Mrs. W. H.
    W. Russell Button, Inc.
    Byrnes, Cornelia Park
    Cady, Mary R.
    Cagney, James
    Cahill, Marion Cotter
    Cahners, Helen R.
    Calder, A.
    California Palace of the Legion of Honor
    California Water Color Society
  - Campbell - Carlson, 1921-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Reel 5853, Frame 669-774)
    Campbell, Charles V. and Isabel
    Campbell, Estelle
    Campbell, Marjorie
    Campbell, Mary Louise
    Campanella, Vincent and Leah
    Cane, Florence
    Canfield, Cass and Jane
    Caniff, Milton
    Cannell and Chaffin, Inc.
    Cannon, Eleanor
    Cantine, Jo
    Canton Art Institute
    Cape Cod Conservatory of Music and Arts
    Carey Printing Company Inc.
    Carlee, R. L.
    Carlen Galleries
    Carleton, Juliet
    Carleton, Peter F.
    Carlson, Carl
    Carlson, J. D.
    Carlson, John F.
    Carlson, S. Ohrvel
  - Carnegie Institute, 1919-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Reel 5853, Frame 777-1148)
  - Carney - Carroll, Jack, 1920-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Reel 5853, Frame 1149-1197)
    Carney, John J.
    Carolan, Anna B.
    Carolina Art Association (See Gibbes Art Gallery)
    Carpenter, J. S.
    Carpenter, O. W.
    Stanley M. Carper Co./Carper Galleries
    Carr, Edith B.
    Carrigan, Mr. and Mrs. Joe B.
    Carrigan, William L.
    Carrington, Omar R.
    Carroll, Georgia F.
    Carroll, Jack
  - Carroll, John and Pinky, 1927-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Reel 5853, Frame 1198-1431)
  - Carson - Chanler, 1925-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Reel 5853, Frame 1432-1530)
    Carson, Marie R.
    Carson Pirie Scott and Co. Galleries
    Carstairs, Carroll
    Carter, Evelyn
    Carter, Mrs. R. M.
    Carter, Stephen
    Carter, Whitford
    Cary, E. L.
    Case, Dorothy
    Cassidy, Robert W.
    Cassingham, Nat
    Casson Galleries
    Catholic Charities Appeal
    Catto, Henry E., Jr.
    Cayton, Susan W.
    Cayuga Museum of History and Art
    Cedar Rapids Art Association
    Central Equities Corporation
    Central Louisiana Art Association
    Century Association
    Ceramicenter
    Chace, Jeanetta Jameson
    Chace, Malcolm G., Jr. and Beatrice
    Chaffey Community Art Association
    Chamberlain, Betty
    Champanier, A. A.
    Chandlee, Anne
    Chandler, Henry
    Chandler, John W.
    Chanler, Robert W.
  - Chapellier Studio - Chase, circa 1924-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Reel 5853, Frame 1531-1565)
    Chapellier Studios/Chapellier Gallery
    Chapin, Horace
    Chapin, James
    Chapman, Edward N.
    Chapman, Mrs. John J.
    Chapman, William Porter
    Chappell, W. Vivian
    Charcoal Club
    Chase, Clara T.
    Chase, Clarence M.
    Chase, Doris
    Chase National Bank/Chase Manhattan Bank
    Chase, Rodney
  - Chatham - Cimiotti, circa 1924-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Reel 5854, Frame 13-80)
    Chatham, John
    Chattanooga Art Association, Inc.
    Cheney, Sheldon
    Cherkasky, Martin
    Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Co.
    Chester, William
    Chestnut, Isabel
    Chicago Evening Post
    Chidsey, Alan
    Child Study Association of America
    Children's Aid and Adoption Society
    Children's Press, Inc.
    Chillingworth, Mrs. Charles
    Chisholm, Hugh J.
    Choat, Mabel
    Christ-Janer, Albert
    Chrysler, Walter P.
    Church, C.
    Church of St. John the Evangelist
    Cichowski, S. R.
    Cimiotti, Mr.
  - Cincinnati Modern Art Society - City of Paris, Rotunda Gallery, 1924-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Reel 5854, Frame 81-199)
    Cincinnati Modern Art Society
    Cincinnati Museum Association/Cincinnati Art Museum
    Circle Gallery
    Cirker's Hayes Storage Warehouse, Inc. (See also Hayes Storage, Packing and Removal Service)
    Citizen's Fidelity Bank and Trust Co.
    City Art Museum of St. Louis
    City College
    City of New York Insurance Co.
    City of Paris, Rotunda Gallery
  - Clancy - Clarke, 1919-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Reel 5854, Frame 200-334)
    Clancy, John
    Clark, Alfred Corning
    Clark, Mr. and Mrs. B. S.
    Clark, Burnet J.
    Clark, Eliot
    Clarkdale Estates, Inc.
    Clarke, Augustus W.
  - Clearwater Art Museum - Cleveland Institute of Art, 1922-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Reel 5854, Frame 335-391)
    Clearwater Art Museum (See also: Florida Gulf Coast Art Center, Inc.)
    Clement, Norman P.
    Clement, Mr. and Mrs. S. Merrell
    Clements, G. H.
    Geoffrey Clements, Inc.
    Clements, George
    Cleveland Institute of Art
  - Cleveland Museum of Art, 1922-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Reel 5854, Frame 392-563)
  - Cleveland School of Art - Cohen, 1924-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Reel 5854, Frame 564-642)
    Cleveland School of Art
    A. B. Closson, Jr., Co.
    Clymer, James Floyd
    Coburn, Mrs. L. L.
    Cocke, Frances H.
    Cocroft, Thomas
    Coe, John I.
    Coe, Theodore
    Coffin, Winthrop
    Cohan, George M.
    Cohee, John F.
    Cohen, Frances
    Cohen, George M.
    Cohen, Lester
    Cohen, Louis D.
    Cohen, Margaret Fox
    Cohen, Nessa
  - Colby College - Colonial Williamsburg, 1926-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Reel 5854, Frame 643-708)
    Colby College
    Colby, Rubin
    Cole, Evelyn E.
    Coleman, David
    Coleman, Glenn O.
    Colgate, Henry A.
    Colin, Ralph F.
    Collectors' Finds (See Walker Galleries)
    Collectors Gallery, Inc.
    College Art Association
    Collins, Alan C.
    Collins, Betty Hoog
    Collins, Carvel
    Collins, Henry J.
    Colonial Williamsburg
  - Colorado Springs Fine Arts Center, 1940-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Reel 5854, Frame 709-799)
  - Colt - Congregation Zichron Ephriam, 1924-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Reel 5854, Frame 800-894)
    Colt, Morgan
    Columbia Grammar School
    Columbia Museum of Art
    Columbia University
    Columbus Art League
    Columbus Gallery of Fine Arts
    Columbus Museum of Arts and Crafts, Inc.
    Colwell, Elizabeth
    Comfort, Mrs. W. W.
    Comingore, Mrs. Robert E.
    Committee of Artists' Societies
    Community Coordinating Council of North Queens
    Community Service Society
    Community Synagogue
    Conacher Galleries
    Concordia Teachers College
    Condon, Frank
    Congregation Bnai Jeshurun
    Congregation Zichron Ephriam
  - Conklin - Conway, 1922-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Reel 5854, Frame 895-931)
    Conklin, R. H.
    Conover, Ethel Wyeth
    Connoisseur
    Conroy, John J.
    Consolidated Edison Company of New York, Inc.
    Consolidated Gas Company
    Contemporary Art
    Contemporary Arts
    Contemporary Arts Association
    Contemporary Arts, Inc.
    Conway, Fred
  - Cook, Howard, 1943-1950; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Reel 5854, Frame 932-1028)
  - Cooper - Corbino, 1923-1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Reel 5854, Frame 1029-1109)
    Cooper, Mary M.
    Cooper School of Art
    Cooper Union for the Advancement of Science and Art
    Copher, Glover H.
    Copley Gallery
    Corbel, Margaret
    Corbino, Jon and Marcia
  - Corcoran Gallery of Art, 1919-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Reel 5854, Frame 1110-1287)
  - Cornelius - Cowles, 1921-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Reel 5854, Frame 1289-1383)
    Cornelius, Marty Lewis
    Cornell University
    Cortissoz, Royal
    Cortright, Frank W.
    Cosmopolitan Club
    Costigan, John E.
    Coubert, Charles R.
    Country Beautiful
    Countway, Miss
    Courier-Journal (Louisville)
    Courtland, S.
    Courtenay, J. C.
    Courvoisier Galleries
    Couse, E. Irving
    Coville, Helen
    Cowden, Wallace H.
    Cowdin, J. Cheever
    Cowie Galleris (See also Biltmore Art Salon)
    Cowles, Maude
  - Cox - Craig, 1924-1947; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Reel 5854, Frame 1384-1502)
    Cox, Hermine M.
    Coykendell, Edward
    Craig, Evelyn
    Craig, Kathleen
    Craig, Robert
    Craig, Thomas
  - Cramer - Crissey, circa 1919-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Reel 5854, Frame 1503-1564)
    Cramer, Konrad
    Cranbrook Academy of Art
    Crane, Bruce
    Crane, Louise
    Crawford, Gretchen C.
    Creative Art
    Creative Studio, Inc.
    Creelman, Alice B.
    Cresmer, William T.
    Crissey, W. Clark
  - Crist - Crump, circa 1919-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Reel 5855, Frame 12-50)
    Crist, Marion Speicher
    Crist, William B.
    Cristofano, Daniel
    Crittenden, Walter H.
    Crossgrove, Roger Lynn
    Crowell, Lucius A., Jr.
    Crowley, Joan A.
    Crowley, Timothy F.
    Crowninshield, Frank
    Crum, Priscilla
    Crumley, Leroy A.
    Crump, Mary E. B.
  - Cue - Cushman, 1924-1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Reel 5855, Frame 51-159)
    Cue
    Culver, Albert B.
    Culver, Charles B.
    Cumings, Thayer
    Cuniff
    Cunningham, John J., Jr.
    Cunningham, Thomas H.
    Currier Gallery of Art
    Curry, Josephine
    Curtis, I. Maynard
    Curtis Publishing Co. (See Ladies' Home Journal)
    Cushman and Wakefield, Inc.
    Cushman Gallery, Inc.
    Cushman, Mrs. Paul
    Cushman, Thelma C.
  - Cuthbert - Cutler, 1927-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Reel 5855, Frame 160-304)
    Cuthbert, Virginia
    Cutler, Carl Gordon
    Cutler, Phoebe
  - D Contemporary Paintings/Dintenfass - Daley, 1922-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Reel 5855, Frame 306-341)
    D Contemporary Paintings/Terry Dintenfass
    Dade, Philip L.
    Daingerfield, Elliott
    Daley, Mrs. L.
  - Dallas Museum of Fine Arts, 1934-1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Reel 5855, Frame 342-422)
  - Dallas Public Library - Davies, 1925-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Reel 5855, Frame 423-497)
    Dallas Public Library
    Dallett, John
    D'Ambarosio Hermanos
    Daniel Gallery
    Danvers Hardware Co.
    Darling, Belle P.
    Darratt, Edward
    Dartmouth College
    Dasberg, Andrew
    Daukas, Nicholas
    Davenport Municipal Art Gallery
    Davey, Randall
    Davey, Mrs. W. N.
    Davidson, Edna C.
    Davidson, Mary P.
    Davidson, Stuart C.
    Davies, Charles T.
  - Davis - Davison, 1919-1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Reel 5855, Frame 498-555)
    Davis, Charles H.
    Davis, Mrs. Chase
    Davis, Dorland and Co.
    Davis, Mrs. Ferdinand
    Davis, Florence
    Davis, Gladys Rockmore
    Davis, Mrs. Henry
    Davis, James A.
    Davis, M. H.
    Davis, Roscoe
    Davis, Warren B.
    Davis, Will J.
    Davison Art Center (See Wesleyan University)
    Davison, H. B.
  - Day - Dayton, 1924-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Reel 5855, Frame 556-641)
    Day, Esther Worden
    Dayton Art Institute
    Dayton, Bruce B.
  - Dealers in American Art - Dennison, 1921-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Reel 5855, Frame 642-715)
    Dealers in American Art
    Dears, Francis D.
    Decorators Club, Inc.
    De Cordova and Dana Museum and Park
    Deeley Gallery
    De Erderly, Francis
    Deerfield Academy
    Deerfield Foundation, Inc.
    DeFord, Ronald K.
    De Forest, Mrs. Shepherd K.
    De Gogorza, Maitland
    De Groot, Adelaide Milton
    DeHaven, Heidi
    Delano, Allen
    Terry DeLapp Gallery, Inc.
    Delaware Art Center
    Isaac Delgado Museum of Art
    Demco Library Supplies
    Deming, Barbara
    Deming, Eleanor
    Deming, Mrs. Q.
    Dempsey, Nan and Mim
    Den Breems, Mrs. Arie
    Denen, Jerri
    Dennington, E.
    Dennison, Carl L.
  - Denver Art Museum - Detroit Artists Market, 1926-1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Reel 5855, Frame 716-822)
    Denver Art Museum
    Des Moines Association of Fine Arts/Des Moines Art Center
    Dessauer, Mrs. W. L.
    Desylva, B. G.
    Desylva, Marie
    Detroit Artists Market
  - Detroit Museum of Art/Detroit Institute of Arts, 1919-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Reel 5855, Frame 823-930)
  - Deutrich - Donnelley, 1919-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Reel 5855, Frame 931-1015)
    Deutrich, Alfred
    Deutsch, Clara
    Devean, Ross R.
    Devere, Bob
    Devine, B.
    Devine, D. J.
    Dewey, Charles Melville
    M. H. De Young Memorial Museum
    Diaz, Jorge C.
    Diaz, Mercedes C.
    Dibblee, Mrs. Benjamin H.
    Dickson, Mrs. Campbell
    Dietz, Julia Grant
    Dill, George A.
    Dill, Otto
    Dillon, Clarence Douglas
    Dintenfass, Terry (See D Contemporary Paintings)
    Dobkin, Alexander
    Dodge, Joseph Jeffers
    Doll and Richards, Inc.
    Donald, Rachel Lenox
    Donaldson, Joseph, Jr.
    Donnelley, Arthur
  - Dordan - Dozier, 1927-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Reel 5855, Frame 1016-1094)
    Dordan, Leonard
    Dorl, Lillian E.
    Dorr, Charles H.
    Dorsey Gallery
    Doubleday and Company, Inc.
    Dougherty, E. Paul
    Downtown Community School
    Downtown Gallery
    Dows, Olin
    Dozier, Joan and William
  - Drawing Society - Eckard, 1920-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Reel 5855, Frame 1095-1191)
    Drawing Society
    Dreyful, Jean
    Driggs, Elsie
    Drought, Marian
    Drummond, Penny
    Du Bois, George E.
    Dubuque Art Association
    Duemmling, Dorothy C.
    Duke, Betty
    Duke University
    Duncan, Bob
    Dunitz Agency
    Roberth Dunthorne and Son
    Duplaix, Jeanne
    Duran, Ross
    Dustin, Silas
    Duval, Herman
    Duveen, Albert
    Duveen Brothers, Inc.
    Duveen-Graham Modern Art
    Duveen, Joseph
    Dwight Hall, Yale University
    Dyer, George J.
    Earle, Dorothy Kirchner
    Earle, Maurice James
    Early, Edward A.
    Eastern Michigan University
    Eastman, John, J., Jr.
    Easton, Joan K.
    Ebb, Fred
    Eckard, Clarence
  - Edelstein - Elson, 1922-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Reel 5855, Frame 1192-1292)
    Edelstein, Babette Bauman
    Edelson, Gilbert S.
    Eden Family
    Edgerly, Beatrice
    Edison, Robert W.
    Edmundson Art Foundation, Inc.
    Edwards, Archibald C.
    Edwards, Robert
    Egginton, F. J.
    Eglington, Mrs.
    Egner, Arthur F.
    Ehrenfast, Fritz
    Ehrenford, Josephine
    Eider, S.R.L.
    1811 House
    Einson-Freemen Co., Inc.
    Eisenberg, A.
    Eisendrath, William N., Jr.
    Eisner, Helen
    Eland, John S.
    Eliot, Alexander
    Eliot, Lucy
    Douglas L. Elliman and Co.
    Elliott, Eleanor T.
    Elliott, M. A.
    Elliott, Mary
    Elliott, Virginia Cuthbert (See Cuthbert, Virginia)
    Ellis, Garland
    Ellwanger, Helen C.
    Elmore, Derrill G., Jr.
    Elson, Hilbert
  - Embry - Englewood Art Gallery, 1920-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Reel 5855, Frame 1293-1429)
    Embry, Lloyd
    Emeking, J. Eliot
    Emert, Mrs. James T.
    Andre Emmerich Gallery, Inc.
    Empire Trust Co.
    Encyclopedia Britannica
    Enderton, M.
    Engel, Michael M.
    Engisch, Joan
    Engle, Nanene Q.
    Englewood Art Gallery
  - Epstein - Ewing, 1921-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Reel 5855, Frame 1430-1502)
    Epstein, Ellen
    Epstein, Louis
    Equitable Life Assurance Society
    Erickson, Edward
    Erickson, Ernest
    Erickson, Pat
    Erie County Pharmaceutical Association
    Erskine, J. D.
    Erskine, John
    Eskin, Annette
    Esquire
    Essex Art Association
    Etnier, Mrs. C. E.
    Etnier, Stephen M.
    Eulau, Milton B. and Harriet K.
    Eustis, Grace H.
    Evans, Bea
    Evans, Charles P.
    Evans, Maurice V.
    Evans, W. H.
    Evanston Art Center and Market
    Evanston Public Museum
    Evansville Public Museum/Evansville Museum of Arts and Sciences
    Everett, Josephine P.
    Everson Museum of Art (See also Syrances Museum of Art)
    Ewing, Alice
  - Fabro - Farr, circa 1926-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Reel 5855, Frame 1504-1561)
    Fabro, Bernice and J. A.
    Faggi, Alfeo
    Fairchild Engine and Airplane Corp.
    Fairweather-Hardin Gallery
    Falck, Alexander D., Jr.
    Famous Artists Corporation
    Famous Artists Course for Talented Young People/Famous Schools
    Fancher, M. Reid
    Fantasy Gallery
    Far Brook School
    Farjean, Harry B.
    Farmer, Henry
    Farnol, Lynn
    William A. Farnsworth Library and Art Museum
    Farr, Finis
  - Farrar, Straus and Giroux, Inc. - Fenster, circa 1926-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Reel 5856, Frame 13-42)
    Farrar, Straus and Giroux, Inc.
    Fath, Joe
    Fay, William L.
    Federation of Modern Painters and Sculptors
    Feeley Advertising Agency, Inc.
    Feldman, Charles K.
    Felin, Charles F.
    Fellers, Josephine
    Felt, Sylvia
    Fenster, G.
  - Ferargil, Inc. - Findlay Galleries, 1917-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Reel 5856, Frame 43-142)
    Ferargil, Inc.
    Ferry, Edith
    Fertig, Lawrence
    Festival of Arts Association
    Fidelity Appraisal Co., Inc.
    Fidelity Storage and Warehouse Co.
    Fidelity Twentieth Century Transportation Co.
    Field Enterprises Educational Corp.
    Fieldston-Ethical Alumni Association (See New York Society for Ethical Culture)
    Fieldston School Arts Center
    Fiene, Ernest
    Fifield, Edith W.
    Fifth Avenue Auction Rooms
    Fifth Avenue Bank
    Fifth Avenue Protective Association
    Figen, Milton
    Fillin, Amy
    Fillin, Walter and Lucille